[Mongo Santamaria's
"Las Guajiras"]
[singing in Spanish]
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Two worlds ♪
♪ We're living in two worlds ♪
♪ My hair is straight
and yours is curls ♪
♪ He's Romeo she's Juliet
and they don't even
know it yet ♪
♪ Two worlds ♪
♪ We're living in ♪
What?
‐ We have pastelitos
in the oven.
Another verse,
they might be flat.
‐ Mm,
laugh now,
but when I become rich
and famous,
I want you to remember
this moment
and your lack of faith.
‐ Who lacks faith?
Pay these when you hit it big.
‐ Yeah.
You got the keys to the truck?
‐ No, no, no, Daniel needs it
for the Connor wedding.
‐ No, I'm making that delivery.
‐ Pop, I told you.
I'm taking Vanessa out
for our anniversary.
‐ Mm, fourth anniversary.
Ask him where she's
making him go.
Paolo's.
Paolo's, the most expensive
place in Miami.
Dinner there is like a weekend
at the Bahamas, right?
‐ Vanessa Princessa, eh?
She makes you take her
to dinners like this yet wonders
why you live at home.
‐ Whoo!
‐ First of all,
she's not making me take her.
Second, I live here because Mom
would have a heart attack
if I moved out before
I was married.
‐ You're getting married?
‐ No one is getting married.
‐ Yeah, but you know
she's expecting a proposal
soon, right?
Mom, that fan looks ridiculous.
Besides, the AC's on fully.
You know, who needs a fridge
when we can just leave
the milk out?
It's only menopause.
‐ I birth you,
I raise you,
I cook for you.
I support every one‐‐
I support every one
of your crazy dreams,
even this DJing thing,
and in return when
my body's betraying me,
this is the thanks I get?
‐ He's the one marrying
a lunatic.
‐ I'm not getting married.
‐ They're right, Daniel.
You can stick your head
in the sand,
but a woman like Vanessa,
pretty soon she's gonna
give you an ultimatum.
‐ Now I have to hear it
from you too?
‐ Well, I worry about you.
‐ You are my little sister.
It's my job to worry about you.
‐ Natalie Garcia,
what do you think you're doing
with that pricing gun?
‐ Uh‐‐
‐ Is your homework done?
‐ Yes.
‐ Calculus too?
‐ Dad, give her a break.
She just wanted to help Mom.
‐ She wants to help her mother,
she'll get into Princeton.
We have already two idiotas
to take over the bakery.
You are smart enough
to be President, eh?
Presidente.
‐ Yo, how come she's always
the genius
and we're the idiotas?
‐ This I ask myself every day.
‐ Daniel, sing with me.
Everybody, sing with me.
♪ Vanessa Princessa ♪
both: ♪ Vanessa Princessa ♪
‐ I know you all think
Vanessa's a bit much,
but she's driven, and that's one
of the things I love about her.
She's smart, ambitious,
and yes,
one day she might be my wife.
But honestly,
tonight is just dinner.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Noa, over here!
Did he cheat on you?
‐ Are you speaking to him?
‐ Just when I think
you've hit rock bottom,
you start digging.
‐ First up, the news breaking
the Internet today.
Reports are Noa Hamilton,
the model turned fashion mogul,
and Colin Davis,
the actor recently chosen
to be the next Batman,
have broken up.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ This coming only days
after photos surface
of Colin
getting a little too cozy
with the costar of his most
recent film, "Red Line."
‐ Ooh!
‐ What a jerk.
‐ Aye, cry me a river.
‐ But Ma‐‐
‐ Por favor.
Her father's a billionaire.
She never worked a hard day
in her life.
‐ She started her own
fashion label when she was 16
and her own cosmetics line
at 18.
Plus, her YouTube channel,
50 million subscribers.
I followed when there
were only 30.
‐ Now, no comment from Noa
on the breakup just yet,
but the Australian entrepreneur
was all smiles last night
at a fundraiser in New York.
‐ ♪ When you hold it down
for me ♪
‐ That's exactly how
your mom looked the day we met.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Yeah, I might ♪
♪ Take you home
with me tonight ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[singing in Spanish]
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I like ♪
[Alvaro Soler's "Loca"]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Para mí, para mí... ♪
‐ In addition
to those selections,
we have our
inspirational tasting
where Paolo channels
his energies into a unique
dining experience for two.
‐ [gasps]
‐ That's $300 per person.
‐ We'll do that.
‐ Give us a minute.
‐ Yes, perhaps a minute.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
[exhales sharply]
It's like a dream come true.
‐ Happy anniversary.
‐ [swoons]
You look so handsome.
[both laughing]
So did you look
at the house I sent you?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ And?
‐ You're the expert.
‐ Okay.
I know it doesn't seem
like a lot,
but I've sold four homes
in that neighborhood this month.
It's the next Little Haiti.
‐ Mm.
‐ I know it's small
and I know it's a wreck,
but we can fix it up.
Think about it.
A place of our own.
For our future.
It's even got room
for a nursery.
‐ [coughing]
‐ Have you decided?
‐ Actually, could you direct me
to the restroom?
‐ Right this way.
‐ Be right back.
♪ ♪
‐ [exhales]
[distant music playing]
[zipper unzipping]
Turn around.
Can't go with you staring.
Mateo's right.
You heard her out there.
Thing is, I feel like if I don't
propose soon, I'm screwed.
At the same time I feel like
if I do propose soon,
I'm screwed.
[scoffs]
I must sound so crazy.
[toilet flushing]
[stall door opening]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[zipper zipping]
[scoffs]
♪ ♪
‐ You know, if you have
to talk yourself into something,
maybe you should
just stop talking.
‐ Excuse me?
‐ You didn't seem like you were
making a lot of headway.
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, you mean when I was on
the phone talking to my brother.
‐ No, I mean when you were
talking to the picture
while you peed.
[both laughing]
‐ You should see what I do
in the shower.
I hold conference calls
with the U. N.
When I really want a challenge,
I'll do it in Japanese.
‐ [speaking Japanese]
‐ Oh, come on.
[both laughing]
‐ First time here?
Try the soup.
Everything else here sucks.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Tu manera
tu manera ♪
‐ How's the soup?
Daniel.
How's the soup?
‐ It's good.
‐ Mm.
‐ How's your‐‐
‐ Oh, it's wonderful.
Everything is wonderful.
‐ ♪ Tu manera
no me puedo controlar ♪
[INNA's "Tu Manera"]
‐ Do you remember
our first date?
You took me to that little
topless bar on 8th
and then we went dancing?
‐ Yeah.
How come we don't dance anymore?
‐ I was waiting all night
for you to kiss me.
Finally I couldn't wait
any longer,
so I just grabbed you.
‐ Even back then,
when you wanted something,
you went right after it.
‐ You like that about me, right?
‐ Sure.
Why?
‐ This is why.
♪ Estoy quemándote
como en la playa
Estoy gustándote ♪
[glass clinking]
May I please have
everyone's attention?
‐ Vanessa, what are you doing?
‐ Tonight marks four years,
four days, and one hour
since Daniel and I fell
in love at first sight.
Aww, he's shy.
It's one of the things
I love about him.
Anyway, he's always teasing me
about being larger than life,
so when he told me we were
coming here to this
amazing restaurant,
I thought,
"What better place than this?"
[guitar strumming]
♪ We were both young
when I first saw you ♪
♪ I close my eyes
and the flashback starts ♪
♪ You're standing there ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I said Daniel take me
somewhere we can be alone ♪
♪ I'll be waiting
all we have to do is run ♪
♪ You'll be the prince
and I'll be the princess ♪
♪ It's a love story
baby just say yes ♪
[applause]
[exhales]
Daniel,
light of my life,
will you marry me?
[crowd swooning]
[giggles]
‐ [chuckling]
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
‐ Daniel.
‐ Sit down, okay?
‐ Once you say yes
and put the ring on my finger.
♪ ♪
‐ I don't wanna answer you
here like this.
‐ Then just give me
a temporary yes
and we'll talk about it later.
♪ ♪
‐ Say yes.
‐ No.
[all groaning]
‐ That's a million views
on YouTube.
‐ Lewis, put the phone away.
‐ Vanessa...
Wait, hang on.
I'll get the check.
‐ Get the check?
Four years, Daniel.
We've been together four years.
What have you been doing
all this time
if you were just gonna say no?
‐ I didn't know, I was‐‐
‐ I'm a woman, Daniel.
I'm a 28‐year‐old woman.
This is what we do.
We diet, we get married,
we have kids,
and we diet again.
Look at what I did
for you tonight.
Look how much I love you.
Is a yes too much?
‐ [gasps]
‐ Everyone, my name
is Vanessa Sanchez.
I can cook,
I have my own business,
and as of this moment,
I am officially single.
‐ Ooh.
‐ [laughing]
‐ Google me
if you're interested.
[dramatic music]
‐ Good for her.
‐ I'm gonna Google her.
♪ ♪
‐ [sighs]
I keep calling,
but she's not answering.
‐ Of course not, bro.
I mean, you dropped
a nuclear bomb on her head.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I'm really proud of you.
I'd never think
of having the balls
to crush her like that.
‐ How soon can you pick me up?
‐ Uh, Daniel, uh,
this is a pretty big gig,
and it's about to start.
Or did you forget?
‐ I'm broke,
I'm soaked,
I'm probably single,
and now I'm gonna have
to walk home.
Is that what you're telling me?
‐ Well, you know,
at least it's a nice night.
[Happy Colors featuring
Magic Juan's "Chévere"]
♪ ♪
‐ What is up, mi gente?
I'm MC Cubano,
and let's get
this party started!
All right, Deering High School.
Let's dance!
‐ Kill me now.
‐ Pump it up!
Pump it up!
[car horns honking]
‐ Slow down.
‐ Are you serious?
You want me to slow down?
‐ Hey.
You want a ride?
Come on.
It's the least I can do.
After all,
I feel kind of responsible.
I did tell you to get the soup.
‐ No, the soup was good,
actually.
I'm taking some home.
‐ Let me take you home.
‐ Oh, here we go.
‐ I meant to his home.
‐ Hamilton, are you serious?
I mean, come on.
‐ What do you say?
In ten seconds,
TMZ's gonna be all over us,
so are you in or are you out?
♪ ♪
[Jaded's "Young"]
‐ ♪ Sipping on that Coke
and rum ♪
‐ So, Daniel,
this is Piper, my best friend,
my stylist Zoe,
and this rude man is my manager,
Lewis.
Ladies, Daniel's
had a really hard night.
I think we should cheer him up,
right?
What do you wanna do?
Anything.
Sky's the limit.
You wanna go somewhere?
‐ How 'bout Bermuda?
‐ We just flew here.
‐ You are so...
‐ [laughing] Stop!
‐ I have to work in the morning.
‐ Relax, Cinderella.
I'll have you home before
you turn into a pumpkin.
What do you wanna do more than
anything in the whole world?
‐ ♪ Ever that we want
'cause we're young ♪
‐ Change my shirt.
‐ Practical man.
How refreshing.
‐ Lewis, can I please
have your shirt?
‐ Uh, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
I beg your pardon?
‐ I know that you're
wearing layers.
‐ This is Gucci.
‐ Please?
‐ [sighs] All right.
If you ever question
how much I love you, Hamilton,
I am going to remind you
of this moment.
‐ I'm so grateful.
‐ This is cashmere.
‐ You're such a snob.
‐ ♪ We can splash out
we can throw it up ♪
♪ We can do whatever that
we want 'cause we're young ♪
‐ Is that making
you uncomfortable?
We can look away.
Girls, look away.
‐ No, I'm gonna keep looking.
‐ Wow.
‐ Keep your eyes on the road,
honestly.
‐ Keep your eyes forward too.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Okay,
that was your first wish.
A shirt.
Now, I'm gonna ask you what
you want for your second wish,
but before that,
I really need your help
with something.
‐ I'm almost afraid to ask.
‐ Oh, he catches on quick.
‐ With what?
‐ My mustache.
[Tove Stryke's "Mistakes"]
‐ ♪ I should probably
leave right ♪
‐ Ooh, yeah.
‐ ♪ You got me buzzing
like a streetlight ♪
‐ Long time.
Good to see you.
Long time.
And this is my new friend,
Daniel.
‐ Daniel.
‐ Daniel, nice to meet you.
[all speaking at once]
‐ ♪ Wanna get close
no clothes ♪
♪ And I don't feel
like going home now ♪
♪ Got me all up
in the zone now ♪
[cell phone buzzing]
♪ Oh baby give me highs
and lows ♪
♪ Wanna get close
no clothes ♪
♪ It's probably better
if I go now ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You make me
you make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
make mistakes
♪ Love how bittersweet
it tastes ♪
‐ Are you doing horns?
Nice.
‐ Never looked better.
‐ ♪ Hey you make me
you make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
make mistakes ♪
‐ Point of no return, brother.
‐ ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
‐ Hey, can I get you anything?
‐ You mean like a gun?
One of those little
kitchen knives
chefs use to dice up carrots
into tiny slices?
‐ [groans]
[glass shattering]
‐ [breathing heavily]
[sighs]
Okay.
Maybe I'm overreacting.
In fairness, my proposal
was more sort of my thing
than his.
I spooked him.
Plus he's Cuban,
so he has that whole
macho thing.
‐ Yes, yes, he does.
‐ Maybe I overstepped
in depriving him
the chance to ask me?
I mean, I know he loves me.
He said he loved the idea
of the house.
He even said he wanted me
to go dancing more,
and everyone knows dancing
is just a metaphor for sex.
‐ After four years
to still have all that passion,
that is incredible.
‐ Right?
Oh, I'm so dramatic,
aren't I?
‐ The greats always are.
‐ Oh!
Poor Daniel.
He's probably curled up
somewhere scared to death
he's lost me forever.
[cans spraying]
‐ [laughs]
Hey. You doing okay?
‐ Is this a typical night?
‐ Uh, with Noa,
there's no such thing.
Well, it's her father's hotel,
and he used her image
without her approval,
so we're turning it into
an image she does approve of.
‐ That's right.
Come down.
[can rattling]
[rope zipping]
[both laughing]
Are you happy you got
in the car?
‐ [laughs]
Ask me when I'm back on Earth.
[both laughing]
Should I worry that you feel
the need to deface yourself?
‐ Should I worry
that when I told you
you could do
anything you want,
the best you could come up with
was change your shirt?
‐ Yeah, but it is a nice shirt.
‐ [laughs]
‐ This is the Gordon hotel,
right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ There's a wedding down there.
My family made the pastries
for it.
[dramatic music]
‐ You're a baker?
‐ My dad has a place
in Little Havana.
Rafael's,
but we all work there.
‐ Who's we?
‐ Me, my brother,
my sister,
and my parents.
‐ Are you all close?
‐ Sometimes maybe too close.
What about you?
♪ ♪
‐ Are you turning my mustache
into a butterfly?
That's amazing.
[can hissing]
‐ I like to paint.
‐ Full of surprises.
♪ ♪
[can hissing]
[machine clicking]
‐ I know.
‐ [moans]
[upbeat music]
‐ [laughing]
[both speaking Spanish]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
‐ Aye, uh‐oh.
Aye, Papa.
That's the home phone.
It must be one of the kids.
Hello?
Is everything all right?
‐ Mari, it's Vanessa.
I'm sorry to disturb you but I
was hoping to talk to Daniel.
‐ Isn't he with you?
‐ No.
So you haven't heard from him
about anything, then?
‐ Why?
Is something wrong?
‐ Que paso?
Baby, que paso?
‐ No.
I‐‐
I wasn't feeling well
so I asked him to take me home.
I just wanted to let him know
my fever broke,
but his phone is off.
Anyway, gotta go.
Bye.
[exhales]
Get ready.
[indistinct chatter]
[Marshmellow and Bastille's
"Happier"]
‐ ♪ Know that means
I'll have to leave ♪
‐ Um, you're‐‐
you're Natalie, right?
‐ ♪ I want to see you smile ♪
‐ Yeah, yeah.
Why?
‐ Just someone said that DJ's
your brother.
♪ ♪
‐ Oh.
I do‐‐
[laughing]
No. What?
No.
No, he's not.
[cell phone ringing]
‐ Mom?
‐ Have you talked
to your brother?
I've been trying to call,
and he's not answering the phone
and Vanessa called here
sounding very strange.
‐ Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's fine.
She proposed to him
and he told her no.
‐ She proposed and he said no?
And you didn't think to call me?
Mateo...
‐ Okay, Mom, Mami, relax.
Listen.
I'll find him and I'll tell him
to call you, okay?
‐ [scoffs]
[cell phone ringing]
‐ Bro, where are you?
Mom's worried
you're gonna kill yourself.
‐ You're not gonna believe this.
I'm hanging off of the side
of a building.
I'm with Noa Hamilton.
She was at the restaurant.
We met in the bathroom,
and now I'm at the Gordon Hotel
painting over
a giant picture of her.
‐ Daniel, Daniel,
I know you're mad at me
for not picking you up,
all right?
So fine.
I'm sorry.
I'll let Mom know
that you're okay.
‐ Hello?
‐ Hey, Noa, hurry up!
You wanna get caught?
There's a crowd gathering.
Let's go.
[Mark Nolan & David Redwitz's
"Freedom to Dance"]
‐ ♪ To dance ♪
♪ ♪
[Camilla Cabello's
"She Loves Control"]
‐ ♪ No she doesn't go
to the bar ♪
‐ You're new, right?
‐ Yeah, yeah.
‐ Do you like it so far?
‐ Honestly, no.
[both laugh]
I haven't really gotten time to,
like, know anyone, so...
‐ Yo, I need your help.
‐ ♪ She wants it her way ♪
‐ Natalie.
Natalie.
If you keep ignoring me,
I'm gonna stand here all night.
Yo, you know everything
about Noa Hamilton, right?
Yes, yeah.
Why?
‐ Do you know if she's in town?
‐ Let me just check her tracker.
No, Mate‐‐hey!
‐ ♪ She wants it her way ♪
♪ And there's no way she'll
ever stay ♪
‐ Holy mother of mothers.
‐ I'm telling mom you did this.
‐ You do that!
[percussive music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
‐ It was her.
I have photos.
‐ Yo, let me see that.
‐ Can I s‐‐
I wanna see that.
Just an emergency, I'm sorry.
[laughing]
[breathing heavily]
You wouldn't happen
to know where they went, huh?
‐ No.
♪ ♪
‐ Is this Julio Z's new place?
‐ You said you were hungry.
‐ Don't fight it.
‐ And here's Julio.
‐ How are you, gorgeous?
‐ You're a lifesaver.
‐ Yeah, don't worry.
Go right in. Hey.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ You wanna talk about it?
‐ No.
‐ Hey. It's me.
I know the difference between
hurt Noa and really hurt Noa.
Okay, fine.
But what are we doing
with baker boy over there?
‐ We're having fun.
‐ Yeah, and when he sells
his story to "The Enquirer"?
‐ You're so paranoid.
‐ So you don't have to be.
‐ Should I just cry myself
to sleep?
‐ These are my options?
Look, when the time comes,
you tell me
and I'll take care of it, okay?
[cell phone rings]
Oh.
[laughs]
Roger, hey.
How would you like an exclusive?
She'll tell her side
of the breakup,
and you get to write
about all the girls' schools
she's funding around the world.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
‐ Leave any room for dessert?
‐ Actually, Daniel here's
a baker, and I was thinking
he could maybe make something
in your kitchen?
‐ Noa, please.
You don't ask a chef‐‐
‐ By all means.
Any friend of Noa
is a friend of mine.
‐ Let's see what you got.
‐ [laughs]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
‐ What?
What's that look?
‐ This is my supportive face.
Really.
[laughs]
All right, you wanna roll it,
not kill it.
Here, let me show you.
So, see?
You just want to give it
a little muscle,
especially on the edges.
See?
I'll flip it for you, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, yeah, yeah.
‐ You know,
just, like, make it rain.
There you go.
‐ Okay.
‐ There it is.
There it is.
‐ Too much guava.
Too much guava?
‐ Yes.
‐ [laughs]
[both chuckling]
How come you're spotless
and I look like a crime scene?
[both laughing]
‐ You should not
be hard on yourself.
Honestly, you've definitely
shown me something.
‐ What?
‐ Most people,
when you ask them
to do something new,
something you know
nothing about,
and they're totally afraid
to look foolish.
But you‐‐
‐ Careful.
‐ You're fearless.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you.
[both laughing]
‐ Mmm‐mmm.
‐ Mmm.
Mmm.
‐ No, no.
We gotta let them cool off.
‐ What are we supposed
to do until then?
‐ We clean.
I know where you should start.
‐ Oh, really?
‐ [laughs]
Oh, careful.
This is Gucci.
‐ Oh, yeah?
You haven't heard?
I'm known to spill things.
‐ Seems that word
of our little feast
has gotten out,
so either you two wrap up
the Great Miami Bake‐Off,
or Julio winds up
with 100 customers
he does not want.
All right?
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
♪ ♪
‐ 24 hours a day they're glued
to their phone,
and now when there's
a real emergency, nothing.
‐ He's fine.
‐ Aye.
‐ They're all fine.
‐ I can't believe she proposed.
I mean,
I can believe she proposed.
I just can't believe
he said no.
[laughs]
‐ And how do we feel about that?
‐ Relieved!
‐ Ah.
Aye, please.
I mean,
she had her good qualities,
but he could do
way better than that.
‐ Vanessa was easy to tease,
but I'm not so sure
she'll be easy to replace.
[keys jingling,
door unlocking]
‐ Oh, it's you.
‐ And you wonder why
I have self‐esteem issues.
‐ No, honey, I'm sorry.
It's just this night
has been crazy.
‐ Yeah, I got that after Mateo
went running from the dance.
[chuckles]
'Cause it wasn't enough
that everyone at that school
thinks that I'm a freak
or a charity case.
No.
Now I'm also the sister
of MC Cubano!
[knocking]
Go away.
‐ Sorry.
You didn't get the mom
that goes away.
You got the mom that smothers.
Sweetheart,
I'm not going to pretend
to understand
what you're going through.
A new school,
honors classes,
but there is one thing
that I do know,
and that is what it's like
to be 15
dealing with teenage boys.
Now, I know the church doesn't
approve of birth control,
but there's nothing wrong with
a woman being prepared and‐‐
‐ Yo, Natalie!
Are you here?
Where's my phone?
‐ Oh, thank God.
‐ Do you have my phone?
‐ Por que?
‐ Here.
You're welcome.
‐ Have you spoken to Daniel?
‐ Can I get some privacy,
please?
‐ [speaking Spanish]
What's going on?
‐ I'm just checking my messages.
‐ Well, is one of them
from Daniel?
‐ Yeah, I just spoke
to him once briefly.
Um...
‐ And?
‐ Okay.
I, um‐‐I need to figure out
how to present
this information to you.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Words.
Use words.
‐ Okay.
As you know,
Vanessa proposed tonight.
And as you know,
Daniel said no.
‐ Mateo, I swear to God,
if you don't start
saying something new,
I'm gonna shove this fan
down your throat.
‐ I have reason to believe...
[crowd cheering]
[upbeat music]
Based on compelling
circumstantial evidence...
‐ One.
‐ Where's Daniel?
‐ That Daniel...
[crowd shouting]
♪ ♪
Is out with Noa Hamilton.
‐ What?
‐ Mami‐‐Mami, Papi, listen.
I know it sounds crazy, okay?
But his story checks out.
‐ Oh, my God.
He's right.
Mateo's right.
‐ Aye, dios mio.
‐ [laughing]
‐ Didn't I tell you?
‐ Daniel.
‐ That was Vanessa.
‐ Daniel, are you home?
‐ [speaking Spanish]
‐ Vanessa.
She's outside.
‐ No, no.
[knocking]
‐ Daniel!
‐ Talk to her.
‐ What do you mean?
[all speaking at once]
‐ I don't know Spanish.
What are you‐‐
what are you telling me?
I'm not‐‐
[all speaking at once]
[knocking]
‐ Daniel, are you home?
‐ Daniel!
[gasps]
Mateo!
‐ Hey, uh, just, uh,
keep it down, okay?
‐ I need to talk to Daniel.
‐ Yeah, here's the thing.
He's asleep.
‐ How can he sleep?
‐ Well, because he's upset.
He's very, very, very upset.
So, you know, I...
Gave him some of the pills that
the doctor prescribed
for my mom's hot flashes.
It knocked him right out, so‐‐
‐ Okay, Mateo, let me in, okay?
Vanessa, I know you think you
need to charge in there
and talk to Daniel
about his incredibly
stupid answer
and reaffirm your love,
but you're wrong,
and I'll tell you why.
‐ Why?
‐ Because you did something
great for my brother.
You did.
Tonight you gave him a chance
to see what life
would be like without you.
And as a result,
the entire family's
spent half the night
worried sick about him.
[dramatic music]
So go home,
get some rest,
and when you both have had
the chance to, like,
sleep this crazy night off,
then come back in the morning.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Tomorrow's a new day.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Okay?
‐ ♪ You got me feeling so good
got me feeling so good ♪
♪ And I know it's kinda crazy ♪
♪ You give me all that I need
and I don't care who sees ♪
♪ Ain't nobody gonna
change that ♪
[Slushii featuring Sofia Reyes's
"Never Let You Go"]
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Some kind of freak ♪
‐ That's Alexi Yevich.
He owns the place.
But he's got nothing on you.
Get down there.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ It's a hard time
finding your freedom ♪
♪ And a long way to go ♪
♪ But I say it's within
your heart
buried in your soul ♪
♪ As long as I'm with you
I'll never let you go ♪
♪ It's within your heart
buried in your soul ♪
♪ As long as I'm with you
I'll never let you go ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's within your heart
buried in your soul ♪
♪ As long as I'm with you
I'll never let you go ♪
♪ It's within your heart
and buried in your soul ♪
♪ As long as I'm with you ♪
♪ Te voy a buscar,
solo tú me puedes salvar ♪
♪ When I'm falling down,
down, down ♪
♪ When I'm falling
down, down, down ♪
♪ Loca voy a quedar
solo tú puedes curar ♪
♪ What I'm going through now ♪
‐ I'm ready for my second wish.
‐ ♪ It's a hard time ♪
‐ Okay.
‐ [laughs]
[cell phone ringing]
‐ Tell me everything,
and don't skip
even a microsecond.
‐ Well, we met
at the restaurant.
Um...
‐ Ooh!
‐ Caught him at a‐‐
a vulnerable moment.
But there was something
about him, you know?
‐ Oh, my God,
Miss Hamilton, you're‐‐
I just think you're amazing
and really talented
and an incredible role model.
And Colin Davis is an ass.
‐ So Daniel tells me that you're
starting at a new school.
I know how hard that can be.
I was always starting
at some new school,
and I always had a tough time
making friends.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah.
But it gets better,
and if you're even half
as charming as your brother,
you'll be fine.
‐ Okay, thank you.
Good‐bye.
All right.
Hey, how was the dance?
‐ Don't talk to me.
Talk to her.
She likes you.
‐ Thank you.
I'll be the cool brother
for months now.
[distant pop music playing]
What?
‐ All night,
my friends and I flirt with you,
and then when I ask you
what your wish is,
it's that I talk to your sister.
‐ When you put it that way,
it sounds pretty bad.
‐ No, I think it sounds great.
When I asked my ex what
he wanted for his birthday,
his wish was a threesome
with my best friend.
‐ That's not cool.
[scoffs]
‐ I should have known better,
you know?
But I just wanted to believe.
Seemed so right
'cause he knew my world
and he knew what it was like.
‐ It should work.
You think it's working,
and then you realize it isn't.
‐ ♪ Without me,
thinking you could live ♪
‐ Are you thinking about
your girlfriend?
‐ About how to be fair to her.
If I even know what fair is.
‐ And what about you, Daniel?
What about what you want?
‐ ♪ Thinking you could live
without me ♪
‐ I guess I want what
my parents have.
It's magic,
the two of them.
They fight,
they have their moments,
but they make each other better.
[dramatic music]
‐ If you really believe
that that's out there,
then you shouldn't settle
for anything less.
Go find it.
‐ It's easy for you to say
when you have an entire world
to choose from.
Me, I don't even have
a passport.
‐ So we'll get you one.
I mean,
you still have a third wish.
‐ [exhales]
♪ ♪
[camera shutters clicking]
‐ Let's go inside, yeah?
Get a drink,
go dance.
♪ ♪
‐ [sighs]
‐ Hey, can you get me a drink?
[Hans Hummer, Max Bronco,
& Andrea Terrano's
"Baila Conmigo"]
♪ ♪
‐ You don't make it easy.
[Georgia's "About Work
The Dancefloor"]
♪ ♪
‐ What, you're stalking me now?
‐ I'm not stalking you.
You wouldn't answer
any of my calls.
‐ So you flew to Miami?
‐ Look, I had to come
and see you to tell you
that none of this is true.
All right?
None of it.
My agent thought it would be
good publicity for the film.
Supposedly it's tracking low
or something.
‐ Oh, please.
The press hates you.
That's why you're here.
‐ Since when do I care
about the press?
Noa, come on.
I just flew
halfway across the planet
to come and tell you
that I love you.
‐ ♪ You want me to stay
a while ♪
‐ Bravo.
Nice performance.
‐ Noa, this is me.
♪ ♪
This is real.
‐ ♪ Dance floor ♪
♪ I was just thinking
about work the dance floor ♪
‐ Leave now and it's a win.
‐ What?
‐ When you do what I do
as long as I've done it,
you get a nose for people.
I think you're a good guy,
Daniel.
That's why it's my hope
that you leave now
before you get humiliated.
‐ I get it, Gucci.
You don't like me.
‐ Sometimes she finds them
at dinner.
Sometimes at a party.
One time she even found somebody
at a hot dog stand
near Rockefeller Center.
Normal guys
who she takes a shine to.
Next thing you know,
they're along for the ride.
She does this after
every heartbreak.
I think she likes to see
the world through your eyes.
Feel your excitement.
And then just when you start
to feel like you might
be friends,
or fall in love,
she has me quietly return you
to your reality.
[dramatic music]
I don't think she realizes
how hard a landing that can be.
You can stay and watch it happen
for the next few hours,
or you can leave now
with your dignity.
♪ ♪
No, no, it's okay.
I'll give you my card.
You can send it to me.
‐ The last thing I want
is anything from any of you.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Whoo‐hoo!
[car horn honking]
‐ Put a shirt on!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
‐ Here you go.
‐ Beautiful.
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Nat, what happened?
‐ Your girlfriend happened.
Uh‐uh.
BoHo Barbie,
you were in the back.
The hashtags.
She's changed our lives.
Hi, sorry about that.
Thank you for waiting.
‐ Oh, my God.
Oh.
[kisses]
The hero returns.
Hey, did you sleep with her?
‐ Hey!
Okay, you don't call
your mother, huh?
‐ Hang on.
Did you?
‐ [exhales]
‐ Yo. Yo!
♪ He's the baker
and she's the beauty ♪
[cell phone chimes]
‐ Why does my phone
keep blowing up
when I'm preparing to be
gracious to give Daniel
a second chance?
What?
‐ ♪ I want you to rule my life
you to rule my life
you to rule my life yeah ♪
♪ I want you to rule my night ♪
[indistinct chatter]
‐ [grunts]
Hey!
‐ Excuse you!
‐ [grunts]
‐ ♪ Then I'll make it
all right yeah ♪
‐ [grunts]
‐ Hey!
‐ ♪ You to rule my life
you to rule my life ♪
‐ Where's Daniel?
‐ Hey, Vanessa.
How was your sleep?
[all oohing]
‐ Where is Daniel?
‐ ♪ I want you
to bring it all on
if you make it all wrong ♪
♪ Then I'll make it
all right yeah ♪
‐ Papa.
Papa.
There's someone here to see you.
Get up.
‐ [grunting]
‐ [speaking Spanish]
‐ ♪ I know you miss me too
like you should ♪
♪ I'll miss you
I wish you
I wish you ooh ♪
‐ ♪ Will come back to
come back to me ♪
♪ Come back to me
Come back to me ♪
♪ ♪
‐ [exhales]
♪ I want you to rule my life ♪
♪ You to rule my life
you to rule my life ♪
♪ I want you to rule my life
you to rule my life
you to rule my life yeah ♪
♪ I want you
to bring it all on ♪
‐ I still owe you a wish.
♪ I want you to rule my life ♪
[chuckles]
‐ ♪ You to rule my life
you to rule my life ♪